Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
His arms now restored by the Queen of Witches, Asta and the others were fighting to protect the forest from enemy forces when they were suddenly confronted by Fauna, a leading member of the Eye of the Midnight Sun who also possesses a third eye.
She's got a third eye too!
Everything is riding on this single shot!
Water creation magic! Sea dragons roar!
Our heroes appeared to be helpless as Fauna's fire spirit, Salamander, began to lay waste to the forest.
But thanks to a powerful attack generated by Noelle's water magic, they were able to subdue the terrible beast.
Okay! Finally time for my special move!
For the finishing blow, Asta used Bulthrust, a fighting technique he had just invented.
Here we go!
Bulthrust!
Manicom
This piece began revealing
Thank you.
So it appears he wasn't all bark and no bite.
And those other troops.
I don't know who this is, but I'm guessing he isn't a witch.
He must have guts to stand up to this huge army all by himself.
Either that or he's stupid.
Mars, you remember me, right?
Wait a minute now.
I might be totally off base here.
I think that guy's our old teacher.
Yes, Landros.
And it looks like I get the honor of tormenting you.
Lucky me.
Me!
Ooh, still got it, huh?
You two have changed quite a bit.
And I can see that it's not for the better.
You leave me no choice.
But to atone for my mistake.
Ooh, feel that breeze?
Nice and gentle.
I'll ask you this one time.
Any chance you'll turn back?
Ha ha ha!
Well, we're the ones with the army, so I'm thinking that's our line.
See, here's the thing.
It turns out our king isn't in the best of health these days.
And from what we've been hearing,
the Queen of Witches has been around for hundreds of years now.
The king wants to find out her secret,
even if it means wiping out everyone in this pitiful forest.
So when we got word that the Eye of the Midnight Sun
was already planning to stir up trouble here,
we thought we might as well take advantage of the confusion
and make this a real party.
We want something.
We take it by force.
That's always been our philosophy in the Diamond Kingdom, right?
Which is why I left and never went back.
Now!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Sure is good to see you again, Teach!
Ha!
All these soldiers finished charging right for us!
Is he crazy?
When creation...
Emperor of Slashing Winds, Winter wins!
Here it comes!
He's fast!
Wait!
I know him!
It's that traitorous coward, Fonzel Kruger.
He was a Diamond Kingdom commander
and combat instructor before he double-crossed us.
And he's got a sizable bounty on his head as well.
Let's take him down now!
They're not moving.
Must be hard to attack when your allies are that close together.
Especially with the powerful magic ability that those two resist.
But there's only so much one man can do.
I'll have to depend on my other half and my student.
I wonder if my master ever put clothes on.
There.
I am such a genius!
Remain calm!
Assume formation number six!
Even if he is a former commander,
if you follow orders and strike from afar,
then he will fall!
He is your only target!
That's not exactly accurate.
No matter how many troops your opponent has,
you should always attack with three times as many.
That's what master told me.
It's an ambush!
We'll be fine.
We have plenty of soldiers.
Go!
Squad two!
What?
They're pushing us into the forest.
There's no way this will work with all these trees and fog.
Let's switch to formation 13!
Squad four!
Squad five!
How are they able to predict our every move?
Easy.
Not so long ago,
I was on the Diamond Kingdom's assassination squad.
You aren't even a challenge.
I used to kill people
who were just doing their best to survive.
Simply so that I could stay alive myself.
Maybe I'm hoping to make up for what I've done.
Or maybe I'm just patting myself on the back.
But still, I'm going to stop you.
You're a damn traitor.
True.
But there's nothing you can say that'll make me change my mind now.
If I back down,
then the person who saved my life won't be very happy with me.
That girl's a fierce one,
jumping right in there and taking command of so many people.
Oh, I agree.
Our Mariela sure is something.
Now for the next phase.
What's happening?
And there you have it.
Thanks to my superior magic items and tinkering skills,
I was able to give those security golems a little upgrade.
That's marvelous.
I'm sure it must have been expensive to pull off them.
You won't believe this,
but the materials only cost me about 3,000 yule each.
That much destruction for so cheap?
What a value.
Now's our chance, ladies.
Don't let those lawless brutes ransack our beautiful forest.
Show them that these witches mean business.
Whoa, whoa.
They set a trap down there thinking we would barrel right into it.
It's probably better if we tread carefully,
but it kind of looks like fun,
so here I go.
Whatever the game is, let's play.
Now then, where could they be?
Uh-oh.
Exactly what I thought you'd do.
That's enough, Ladros.
Windbinding magic.
Emperor of slashing winds.
Whirlwind.
Aw, rats.
Guess you got me.
For the last time,
do you want to turn around?
Hmm.
Now where would be the fun in that?
I've got so much more slaughtering left to do.
What's wrong with you?
Huh?
You can't train us to be killing machines
only to expect us to behave like upstanding citizens
and during a big battle like this?
I'm sorry,
but I promised.
See, I told my last pupil,
someone younger than you.
I'm done running.
I'm gonna live.
That's it.
Feel your opponent's mana.
Hmm.
Hmm?
Calm your emotions.
Good job.
Try to focus.
Listen.
Your powers are meant for protecting people
and nothing else.
Don't ever forget that, okay?
Right!
His strength was physical reinforcement spells.
I'll never win like this.
Don't move or you're dead.
Mars.
Of all the students I taught,
he was the most skilled.
There's no way I stand a chance against him at this distance.
I'll have to make some room.
Wind creation magic.
Emperor of slashing winds.
Mountain wind!
Wind creation magic.
I'm putting my all into this.
Now, wind creation magic.
Emperor of slashing winds.
Not having an elemental attribute always made him feel a little odd.
Sir?
I don't need an attribute to be strong, right?
He gave himself a complex over it.
But he still had greater power than any of his peers.
If he knows a long-range spell, I'm done for.
I'd better put him out quick.
Forgive me.
No!
Stop it!
I can't!
No more of your magic, sir!
Please!
I'm downright stuffed.
Are you surprised?
There's not a scratch on him.
Yeah, I've made a few changes.
After you left, the army gave me one of those upgrade surgeries, and I came out with some new tricks.
Absorption and a mission.
My body could suck up any magic attack that's thrown at it, and I can release that gathered force whenever I like.
You know what that means, right?
Not only am I about to kill all your little buddies, I'm gonna use your magic to do it!
What's this power from?
It's not just Ladros.
There's so much, it must be something else.
By the way, Teach, you didn't happen to bring any loved ones into the forest, did you?
Because if you did, you might want to go check on them real quick.
And you'll have to outrun my magic, so you'd better hurry up!
On your marks, get set, go!
Million lasers!
Oh, whoopsie!
I got so excited there that I wiped out my own guys!
I wonder if Teach made it!
Ah, there you are!
Sal!
Oh no!
Domino!
Look at that!
So you did have someone special here, after all.
But why haven't you introduced us?
Don't you have any manners?
Wow!
You didn't tell me your lady friend was such a looker!
I'm jealous!
Hey, wait!
Haven't I seen you before?
Oh yeah!
That's right!
You're the little minx he decided to run away with, aren't you?
So, how have you been?
Ladros, stop!
Please, I beg you.
Use your power for what's right!
Of course!
I am, and I always have!
Come on, you and I both know that combat training was never meant to teach us how to protect anybody!
There's nothing better than using your power to the absolute max and devastating any opponent that dares stand in your way!
My goal is to be recognized all over this nation, and eventually the whole world!
That's why I trained hard and rose through the ranks to become one of the eight shining generals!
Why are you always spewing this idealistic garbage?
No wonder you were defeated in that power struggle and had to flee the Diamond Kingdom with your tail between your legs!
You're such a coward!
Shut your mouth right now!
My cell is no coward!
I think I'll start by killing this noisy little witch!
I think I'll try to kill you!
Domino!
My powers are for protecting people.
people. Everything that you said, well, I guess it finally hit home. Mars, I...
Hey, you're kidding. What is this? There's no need for all this killing. We're all here
for the Queen, remember? Oh, now you want to pull out the kid gloves? Come on! They turned
their backs on the Diamond Kingdom! If we overlook that, then it means we're basically
traitors too. That's fine. Really? You're gonna betray your country? That seems to be
the case. Yay for me! Now I can kill you illegally! You've been a thorn in my side for too damn
long. So good at everything and so nonchalant about it at the same time and such a pain
in the neck. I always knew that if I kept aiming for the top, you would end up getting in my
way somehow. And today's finally my chance! I get to kill you and our old teacher! This
is the best! Mariela? He's my teacher too, you know. Don't treat him like he's some
sort of bonus kill. Why don't you and your pathetic magic stay out of this? That's not
even enough to snack on. There's our little Marsy boy for you! I'll take all that power
and set it back with interest! Flame recovery magic! Phoenix robe! But Mars, why would you
help us? Why would you help us? Ladros is right. The two of us are traitors. I mean, losing
your memories. Not to worry, sir. I've decided I'm on your side. Unexpected though our reunion
may be. We can talk later. First, we should deal with him. Okay. But how do we handle somebody
who can do that? Well, he's almost invincible, but I know of a few ways we can defeat him. One
is to keep feeding him more magic than he can absorb until he self-destructs. We'd have
to use spirit magic or get the queen of witches to help us. The other way is anti-magic.
Anti-magic? Asta, that's right. It turns out we know just the guy and he happens to be waiting
at the opposite end of the forest as we speak. Let's try to guide Landros there. Good
idea, Master. Hey! Are you guys talking about me? Doesn't matter how great your plan is,
it'll be useless against my magic! What then? Huh? Your power is what causes you to be careless.
Oh, I've got a knack for reinforcement spells myself. So say goodbye!
It's over! We've got you completely surrounded! So you might as well give up!
Hot, hot! Don't bother putting up a fight! We don't want to hurt you, so please don't force
us two! You're still young, right? There's no point in you throwing your life away! If
you do something stupid, then your friends and family are gonna be really sad! You're disgusting
human. Don't you dare speak of my friends!
And what do you do? Don't worry, Danny!
No, don't worry, Danny!
Don't worry, Danny! Thank you, Danny!
I'll use Minion Plus, Freunde.
Yeah,ileri!
Oh!
Thank you.
Oh, there's no way he teaches in his 20s.
He's 38.
Nobody could teach sword fighting like that without a ton of experience.
I'd say he's 42.
Not that I care or anything, but I think he's 46.
You guys are forgetting about his beautiful and intelligent fiance, Dominante.
She's the kind of classy lady you can only score with the flirting techniques of a middle-aged man.
Hmm, 50.
You look so tired all the time.
I guess 54.
You are younger than me, at least.
Aren't you?
Guys, I'm only 28.
What you said, well, it really hit home.
Salamander is still alive and well.
So watch now, little one.
Show us what you can do.
Black Clover, page 61.
The Promised World.
My magic is being of unknown age.